<Document>
<<<<<<< HEAD
# Двигатель антиматерии (ДАМ)

Двигатель антиматерии — один из самых простых в применении генераторов электроэнергии. Соберите мультиблоковую структуру генератора на небольшой площади, закиньте баллон топлива, и всё готово. Однако, это не означает что этот тип генератора является полностью безопасным, потенциальной опасностью является риск его перегрева.
=======
  # Antimatter Engine (AME)
  The Antimatter Engine is a short-term support generator for the station, providing a sizable chunk of power for a limited time.

  It's mainly used to assist engineers in starting up bigger engines like the [textlink="Singularity Engine" link="SingularityEngine"] or [textlink="Tesla Engine" link="TeslaEngine"], by supplementing the station's [textlink="batteries" link="PowerStorage"] with partial power to extend their runtime.
>>>>>>> upstream/master

## Строительство
<Box>Требуемые компоненты:</Box>
<Box>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack"/>
<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeJar"/>
</Box>

<<<<<<< HEAD
Начните сборку ДАМ с установки и закрепления контроллера ДАМ на ВВ кабеле. На многих станциях в генераторных на полу имеются решётчатые мостики, которые упростят понимание где что, и куда. Разложите части ДАМ квадратом минимум 3 на 3, старайтесь максимизировать количество "центральных" ядер ДАМ, такие ядра должны быть окружены другими частями со всех 8-ми сторон.

Разложив, воспользуйтесь мультитулом чтобы превратить части ДАМ в его экранирование, что должно завершить создание двигателя антиматерии. Затем, поместите баллон топлива ДАМ в контроллер ДАМ, установите расход топлива на [color=#a4885c]количество ядер умноженное на два[/color] (или меньше) и переключите впрыск.

## Экономия топлива
Чем ближе вы к идеальному соотношению [color=#a4885c]1:2[/color] (1 ядро ДАМ к 2 впрыскам топлива), тем эффективнее будет ваша работа. Вы снижаете эффективность использования топлива до [color=#a4885c]50% и менее[/color], если используете больше ядер, но меньше скорость впрыска топлива.
Например, [color=#76db91]3 ядра и 6 впрыска[/color] будут генерировать [color=#76db91]240 кВт[/color], а [color=#f0684d]8 ядер и 8 впрыска[/color] будут генерировать [color=#f0684d]160 кВт[/color]. Генерируя на 80 кВт меньше, тратя на 2 топлива больше при каждом впрыске.

## Модернизация ДАМ

Как правило, модернизировать ДАМ можно только за счет увеличения количества ядер, что можно сделать, заказав дополнительные ДАМ пакеты в [color=#a4885c]отделе снабжения[/color].
=======
  The AME Controller is the part of the AME that outputs power to the station's grid through an [textlink="HV connection" link="VoltageNetworks"].
  Because of this, you'll want to start your AME construction with the controller on top of an [color=orange]HV wire[/color].

  Most stations have exposed [color=orange]HV wiring[/color] or designated spots to wrench an AME controller, so that it connects to the grid.

  AME shielding is the physical structure that makes the antimatter engine. It's made by converting AME flatpacks into shielding using a multitool.

  To construct an AME, start putting down a 3x3 or larger square of AME flatpacks in preparation for construction, making sure to maximize the number of "center" pieces that are surrounded on all eight sides.
  The greater amount of center pieces, the more cores your AME will have, and the more power it will be able to output safely.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmePartFlatpack" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  Once this is done, you can use a multitool to convert each AME flatpack into shielding, which should form a finished AME configuration.

  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeController" Caption=""/>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AmeShielding" Caption="" Margin="0"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
    [color=#999999][italic]An example of a one core setup[italic][/color]
  </Box>

  ## Operation
  To start the AME, insert a fuel jar into the AME controller, and set the safe injection rate.

  The safe injection rate is the point where the AME can safely run without overheating, while maximizing power output.

  This rate is always twice the core count.

  For example, an AME with one core will have a safe injection rate of 2. With two cores, the safe injection rate would be 4, and so on.

  Any more than this ratio will eventually result in the engine [color=#ff0000]overheating[/color] and, shortly afterwards, [color=#ff0000]exploding[/color].

  The AME controller will [textlink="report" link="InspectingPower"] on both the amount of power it is providing to the grid, and the theoretical maximum power it could provide if demanded.
>>>>>>> upstream/master

</Document>
